Guide to the Stan Steiner Papers, ca. 1940-1987 M0700
Stanford University. Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series XI. Publications
  - Arizona State Department of Public Instruction. "Annual Conference of the Co-ordinating Council for Research in Indian Education" 1963 Apr. 18 -19 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Artists of the Old West catalog.--No. 2 (1974) 1974 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Avineri, Shlomo. "Homo Faber," in The Social and Political Thought of Karl Marx. London: Cambridge University PRess [1968], 65-95 1968 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Bailin, Roxanne. "One of the last human hunts of civilization, and the basest and most brutal of them all: H. H. Bancroft, Foremost Historian on Early California" San Francisco: Company and Sons 1971 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Basta! La Historia de Nuestra Lucha. Delano, CA: Farm Worker Press 1966 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Bathke, Alice and Jerry. "They call themselves 'The people'," University of Chicago magazine.--Vol. 41, no. 5 (1969 Mar. - Apr.), 2 - 17 1969 Mar. -Apr. (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - The beginning of the War on Poverty: A Report on poverty programs in New Mexico. s.l.: State Division of Economic Opportunity 1966 June (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Bernstein, Irving. "Labor relations in Los Angeles," Los Angeles: Institute of Industrial Relations, UCLA 1965 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Bruchac, Joseph. "The Manabozho Poems," The Blue Cloud Quarterly.--Vol. 20, no. 3 (1974) 1974 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Bullock, Paul. "Poverty in the Ghetto and Poverty in Los Angeles," Los Angeles: Institute of Industrial Relations, UCLA 1966 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Cahn, Edgar S. & Jean Camper. "The new sovereign immunity," Harvard Law Review.--Vol. 81, no. 5 (1968 Mar. ) [reprint] 1968 Mar. (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - CALA: Community Action on Latin America.--Vol. 2, no. 2 (1972 Nov.) 1972 Nov. (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - California Migrant Master Plan Progress Report 1966 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - California State Association of Settlements and Neighborhood Centers newsletter 1966 Winter (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Californians of Spanish Surname. San Francisco: Department of Industrial Relations, Division of Fair Employment Practices [2 copies] 1964 May (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Cambridge University Press catalogue: New and Recent books on Latin America and the Caribbean 1984 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Carta Editorial 1964 Aug. 10 -1969 Dec. (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Carver, Raymond. "Sixty Acres: a story," Discourse... a review of Liberal Arts (1969 Winter) [offprint] 1969 Winter (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Catalyst.--No. 4 (1969 Spring) 1969 Spring (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Central Clearing House: A report on our activities to help preserve the environment of New Mexico and the Southwest 1972 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Chicano Studies Center publications Spring sale catalogue 1975 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Choate, Robert B. & Lorraine W. Frank. National Conference on Poverty in the Southwest 1965 Jan. 25 -26 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Christianity Today.--Col. 12, no. 4 (1967 Nov. 24) 1967 Nov. 24 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - The civil rights status of Spanish-speaking Americans in Kleberg, Nueces, and San Patricio Counties, Texas 1967 July (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Clergy and Laymen Concerned newsletter c. 1970 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Communities in Action.--Vol. 2, mp. 2 (1967 Mar.) 1967 Mar. (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Conference on antipoverty programs for migrant and seasonal farm workers proceedings 1966 Jan. 18 -20 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Con Safos.--Vol. 1, no. 1 (1968 Summer) 1968 Summer (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Con Safos.--Vol. 1, no. 2 (1968 Fall) [3 copies] 1968 Fall (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Con Safos.--Vol. 1, no. 4 (1969) 1969 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - "The consequesces of the war," Saturday Review. 1972 Nov. 18 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - CPU [Children's Peace Union] News.--No. 9 n.d. (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - de Cordova, Lorenzo. "Echoes of the Flute," Santa Fe: Ancient City Press 1972 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Council on Economic Priorties annual report 1973 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Council of Shaman Chief Kilpou of the Children of Light and the Great Algonquin Nation of the Ulnoo n.d. (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Cowan, Paul. "Jews without money, revisited," Village Voice (1972 Sept. 21 - 28) [reprint] 1972 Sept. 21 -28 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Critique of the Sunbell Task Force report 1974 Feb. 8 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - The Cultural Reporter.--No. 8 (1974 Oct.) 1974 Oct. (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Daily Review of Soviet Press.--Vol. 6, no. 33 (1960 Apr. 22) 1960 Apr. 22 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Dale, Ralph Alan. "The Future of Music: an investigation into the evolution of forms," Journal of Aesthetics and Art Criticism.--Vol. 26 (1968 Summer) 1968 Summer (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - The Dan Smoot Report.--Vol. 7, no. 31 (1961 July 31) 1961 July 31 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Davis, Leslie B. "Peyotism and the Blackfeet Indians of Montana: an historical assessment" 1961 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Dennis, Eugene, 1905-. Ideas they cannot jail. Introd. by William Z. Foster. New York, International Publishers [1950]. 192 p. 21 cm. 1950 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Department of the Interior news releases 1968 -1974 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Diamond, Stanley. "In search for the primitive," Man's Image in Medicine and Anthropology [offprint] n.d. (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Disadvantaged Mexican American Children and Early Educational Experiences 1968 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - DNA [Dinebeiina Nahiilna be Agaditahe] Newsletter.--Vol. 7, no. 1 (1974 Jan. 30) 1974 Jan. 30 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - DNA [Dinebeiina Nahiilna be Agaditahe] Newsletter.--Vol. 7, no. 3 (1974 Apr.) 1974 Apr. (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Doble Digest of Bilingual Education 1968 Apr. (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Dodge, Natt N. Saguaro National Monument, Arizona Natural History Handbook.--No. 4 n.d. (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Early American Newsletter of the California Indian Education Association.--Vol. 7, no. 3 (1974 May - June) 1974 May -June (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Early American Newsletter of the California Indian Education Association.--Vol. 7, no. 5 (1974 Nov.) 1974 Nov. (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Early Man.--No. 3 (1974 Aug.) 1974 Aug. (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - EDF letter: a report to members of the Environmental Defense Fund 1974 May (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Ehrlich, Howard J. Politics of news media control.-- Research group one, report no. 15 n.d. (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Elizondo, Virgil P. "Religious practices of the Mexican American Catechesis" 1974 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Engels, Friedrich. "The part played by labor in the transition from ape to man," in Dialectics of Nature. New York: International Publishers, 170 - 172, 279 - 296 1940 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Environmental News 1973 Nov. (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - The Episcopalian.--Vol. 135, no. 2 (1970 Feb.) 1970 Feb. (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Ethnic communities in greater Detroit [1 of 2] n.d. (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Ethnic communities in greater Detroit [2 of 2] n.d. (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Everyday life.--Vol. 9, no. 12 (1914 Sept.) 1914 Sept. (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Facts for women.--Vol. 1, no. 1 (1943 Feb.) 1943 Feb. (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Facts for women.--Vol. 1, no. 9-10 (1943 Oct. - Nov.) 1943 Oct. -Nov. (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Facts for women.--Vol. 1, no. 11 (1943 Dec.) 1943 Dec. (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Facts for women.--Vol. 2, no. 1-2 (1944 Jan. - Feb.) 1944 Jan. -Feb. (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Facts for women.--Vol. 2, no. 3 (1944 Mar.) 1944 Mar. (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Facts for women.--Vol. 2, no. 8 - 10 (1944 Aug. - Oct.) 1944 Aug. -Oct. (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Farming terraced land.--U. S. Department of Agriculture leaflet no. 335 n.d. (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Ferdon, Edwin N. "A trial survey of Mexican Southwestern architectural parallels" Santa Fe 1955 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - First session working group on indigenous populations 1982 Aug. 9 -13 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Forbes magazine.--Vol. 136, no. 11 (1985 Oct. 28) [includes: Steiner, Stan. "Santa Fe Land Rush," pp. 74-79] 1985 Oct. 28 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Ford Foundation letter.--Vol. 4, no. 5 (1973 Aug. 1) 1973 Aug. 1 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Fort Peck, Bureau of Indian Affairs, ten year development program 1964 Sept. 25 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Fortune News. 1971 Oct. (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - The Frontier Military Catalog.--No. 3 (1978 Sept.) 1978 Sept. (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - "Gente que camina con las Cosechas," Washington, D.C.: U.S. Commission on Civil Rights 1979 Mar. (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - "George McGovern talks," Life 1972 July 7 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - A Glimpse of Chino [pamphlet] Hurley, NM: Copper Corporation n.d. (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - El Grito: a journal of contemporary Mexican American Thought.--Vol. 1, no. 4 (1968 Summer) 1968 Summer (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - El Grito del Norte.--Vol. 6, no. 6 (1973 July - Aug.) 1973 July -Aug. (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Hall, Gus. "The colonial plunder of Puerto Rico," New York: New Outlook Publishers 1972 Dec. (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Heffer catalogue.--No. 172 Social Anthropology n.d. (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Heffer catalogue.--No. 176 Africa south of the Sahara n.d. (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Heffer catalogue.--No. 182 History and politics 1984 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 4, no. 3 1941 Oct. 27 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 4, no. 5 1941 Nov. 10 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 4, no. 6 1941 Nov. 17 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 4, no. 7 1941 Nov. 24 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 4, no. 8 1941 Dec. 1 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 4, no. 10 1941 Dec. 15 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 4, no. 12 1941 Dec. 29 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 4, no. 14 1942 Jan. 12 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 4, no. 15 1942 Jan. 19 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 4, no. 17 1942 Feb. 2 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 4, no. 22 1942 Mar. 9 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 4, no. 26 1942 Apr. 6 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 5, no. 3 1942 Apr. 27 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 5, no. 5 1942 May 11 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 5, no. 6 1942 May 18 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 5, no. 7 1942 May 25 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 5, no. 8 1942 June 1 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 5, no. 9 1942 June 8 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 5, no. 10 1942 June 15 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 5, no. 12 1942 June 29 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 5, no. 13 1942 July 6 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 5, no. 15 1942 July 20 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 5, no. 16 1942 July 27 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 5, no. 24 1942 Sept. 21 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 5, no. 25 1942 Sept. 28 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 5, no. 26 1942 Oct. 5 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 6, no. 1 1942 Oct. 12 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 6, no. 2 1942 Oct. 19 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 6, no. 3 1942 Oct. 26 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 6, no. 4 1942 Nov. 2 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 6, no. 5 1942 Nov. 9 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 6, no. 6 1942 Nov. 16 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 6, no. 7 1942 Nov. 23 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 6, no. 8 1942 Nov. 30 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 6, no. 9 1942 Dec. 7 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 6, no. 10 1942 Dec. 14 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 6, no. 11 1942 Dec. 21 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 6, no. 12 1942 Dec. 28 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 6, no. 13 1943 Jan. 4 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 6, no. 14 1943 Jan. 11 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 6, no. 15 1943 Jan. 18 (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 6, no. 16 1943 Jan. 25 (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 6, no. 17 1943 Feb. 1 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 6, no. 18 1943 Feb. 8 (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 6, no. 19 1943 Feb. 15 (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 6, no. 20 1943 Feb. 22 (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 6, no. 21 1943 Mar. 1 (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 6, no. 22 1943 Mar. 8 (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 6, no. 23 1943 Mar. 15 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 6, no. 24 1943 Mar. 22 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 6, no. 26 1943 Apr. 5 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 7, no. 1 1943 Apr. 12 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 7, no. 2 1943 Apr. 19 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 7, no. 3 1943 Apr. 26 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 7, no. 4 1943 May (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 7, no. 5 1943 May 10 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 7, no. 6 1943 May 17 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 7, no. 7 1943 May 24 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 7, no. 8 1943 May 31 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 7, no. 10 1943 June 14 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 7, no. 11 1943 June 21 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 7, no. 12 1943 June 28 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 7, no. 16 1943 July 26 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 7, no. 19 1943 Aug. 16 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 7, no. 20 1943 Aug. 23 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 7, no. 21 1943 Aug. 30 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 7, no. 23 1943 Sept. 13 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 7, no. 24 1943 Sept. 20 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 7, no. 25 1943 Sept. 27 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 7, no. 26 1943 Oct. 4 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 8, no. 1 1943 Oct. 11 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 8, no. 2 1943 Oct. 18 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 8, no. 3 1943 Oct. 25 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 8, no. 4 1943 Nov. 1 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 8, no. 5 1943 Nov. 8 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 8, no. 7 1943 Nov. 22 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 8, no. 9 1943 Dec. 6 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 8, no. 10 1943 Dec. 13 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 8, no. 11 1943 Dec. 20 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 8, no. 12 1943 Dec. 27 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 8, no. 13 1944 Jan. 3 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 8, no. 14 1944 Jan. 10 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 8, no. 15 1944 Jan. 17 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 8, no. 16 1944 Jan. 24 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 8, no. 18 1944 Feb. 7 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 8, no. 19 1944 Feb. 14 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 8, no. 20 1944 Feb. 21 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 8, no. 21 1944 Feb. 28 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 8, no. 22 1944 Mar. 6 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 8, no. 25 1944 Mar. 27 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 8, no. 26 1944 Apr. 3 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 9, no. 1 1944 Apr. 10 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 9, no. 2 1944 Apr. 17 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 9, no. 3 1944 Apr. 24 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 9, no. 4 1944 May 1 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 9, no. 5 1944 May 8 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 9, no. 6 1944 May 15 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 9, no. 7 1944 May 22 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 9, no. 8 1944 May 29 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 9, no. 9 1944 June 5 (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 9, no. 10 1944 June 12 (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 9, no. 11 1944 June 19 (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 9, no. 12 1944 June 26 (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 9, no. 13 1944 July 3 (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 9, no. 14 1944 July 10 (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 9, no. 15 1944 July 17 (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 9, no. 16 1944 July 24 (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 9, no. 17 1944 July 31 (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 9, no. 18 1944 Aug. 7 (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 9, no. 19 1944 Aug. 14 (Box 5, Folder 62)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 9, no. 20 1944 Aug. 21 (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 9, no. 21 1944 Aug. 28 (Box 5, Folder 64)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 9, no. 22 1944 Sept. 4 (Box 5, Folder 65)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 9, no. 23 1944 Sept. 11 (Box 5, Folder 66)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 9, no. 24 1944 Sept. 18 (Box 5, Folder 67)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 9, no. 25 1944 Sept. 25 (Box 5, Folder 68)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 9, no. 26 1944 Oct. 2 (Box 5, Folder 69)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 10, no. 1 1944 Oct. 9 (Box 5, Folder 70)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 10, no. 2 1944 Oct. 16 (Box 5, Folder 71)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 10, no. 3 1944 Oct. 23 (Box 5, Folder 72)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 10, no. 4 1944 Oct. 30 (Box 5, Folder 73)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 10, no. 5 1944 Nov. 6 (Box 5, Folder 74)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 10, no. 7 1944 Nov. 20 (Box 5, Folder 75)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 10, no. 11 1944 Dec. 18 (Box 5, Folder 76)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 10, no. 13 1945 Jan. 1 (Box 5, Folder 77)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 10, no. 15 1945 Jan. 15 (Box 5, Folder 78)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 10, no. 18 1945 Feb. 5 (Box 5, Folder 79)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 10, no. 21 1945 Feb. 26 (Box 5, Folder 80)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 10, no. 23 1945 Mar. 12 (Box 5, Folder 81)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 10, no. 24 1945 Mar. 19 (Box 5, Folder 82)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 10, no. 25 1945 Mar. 26 (Box 5, Folder 83)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 11, no. 17 1945 July 30 (Box 5, Folder 84)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 12, no. 3 1945 Oct. 22 (Box 5, Folder 85)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 12, no. 9 1945 Dec. 3 (Box 5, Folder 86)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 12, no. 11 1945 Dec. 17 (Box 5, Folder 87)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 12, no. 13 1945 Dec. 31 (Box 5, Folder 88)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 12, no. 14 1946 Jan. 7 (Box 5, Folder 89)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 12, no. 16 1946 Jan. 21 (Box 5, Folder 90)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 12, no. 19 1946 Feb. 11 (Box 5, Folder 91)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 12, no. 20 1946 Feb. 18 (Box 5, Folder 92)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 12, no. 21 1946 Feb. 25 (Box 5, Folder 93)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 12, no. 22 1946 Mar. 4 (Box 5, Folder 94)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 13, no. 3 1946 Apr. 22 (Box 5, Folder 95)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 13, no. 4 1946 Apr. 29 (Box 5, Folder 96)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 14, no. 10 1946 Dec. 9 (Box 5, Folder 97)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 14, no. 12 1946 Dec. 23 (Box 5, Folder 98)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 14, no. 21 1947 Feb. 24 (Box 5, Folder 99)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 14, no. 25 1947 Mar. 24 (Box 5, Folder 100)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 15, no. 2 1947 Apr. 14 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 15, no. 7 1947 May 19 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 15, no. 10 1947 June 9 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 15, no. 11 1947 June 16 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 15, no. 13 1947 June 30 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 15, no. 14 1947 July 7 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 15, no. 15 1947 July 14 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 15, no. 16 1947 July 21 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 15, no. 17 1947 July 28 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 15, no. 18 1947 Aug. 4 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 16, no. 2 1947 Oct. 13 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 16, no. 4 1947 Oct. 27 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 16, no. 6 1947 Nov. 10 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 16, no. 7 1947 Nov. 17 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 16, no. 9 1947 Dec. 1 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 16, no. 10 1947 Dec. 8 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 16, no. 11 1947 Dec. 15 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 16, no. 12 1947 Dec. 22 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 16, no. 13 1947 Dec. 29 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 16, no. 14 1948 Jan. 5 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 16, no. 16 1948 Jan. 19 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 16, no. 18 1948 Feb. 2 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 16, no. 19 1948 Feb. 9 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 16, no. 22 1948 Mar. 1 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - In Fact.--Vol. 17, no. 15 1948 July 12 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - In memoriam: Haniel Long. A Special supplement to the Sunstone Review.--Christmas 1974 1974 Dec. (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - El Independiente and the New MExico Independent.--Vol. 78, no. 17 1974 Feb. 15 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Indian Education: the early years conference 1966 Nov. 15 -16 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Indian Forerunner: Eight Northern Indian Pueblos newsletter.--Vol. 3, no. 1 1974 Jan. (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Indian Forerunner. 1974 Fall (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Indian Land: New Mexico Inter-tribal Indian ceremonial n.d. (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Indian Life.--Vol. 6, no. 3 n.d. (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Indian Life.--Vol. 40, no. 1 1961 Aug. (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Indian Record.--Special issue 1974 Aug. (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Info-Red: National Indian Youth Council.--Vol. 1, no. 1 1974 Apr. (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Institute for Advanced Study in Rational Psychotherapy 1974 Feb. -Sept. (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - I.R.C.D. [Information Retrieval Center on the Disadvantaged] Bulletin.--Vol. 2, no. 1 1966 Jan. (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - I.R.C.D. [Information Retrieval Center on the Disadvantaged] Bulletin.--Vol. 5, no. 3 1969 Summer (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - John F. Kennedy Center for the Performing Arts Footlight.--Vol. 2, no. 12 1964 June (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - La Gaceta.--Vol. 5, no. 1 1970 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - La Raza!: Why a Chicano party? Why Chicano Studies? Pathfinder Press (A Merit Pamphlet) 1970 Mar. (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - A Kindergarten curriculum guide for Indian Children: A Bilingual - Bicultural Approach. Bureau of Indian Affairs, Division of Education 1968 Sept. (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Knowlton, Clark S. "Land grant problems among the State's Spanish-Americans," New Mexico Business 1967 June (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Koczkar, Erno. Innovation movement in Hungary. National Inventions office 1950 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Labor Research Association. The Burden of Taxes. New York: International Publishers 1956 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Latin Quarter.--Vol. 1, no. 2 1975 Jan. -Feb. (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Leavell Spotlight.--Vol. 15, no. 1 1974 Spring (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Lenin, Vladimir Ilich, 1870-1924. The state, a lecture delivered to the students of Sverdlov University, July 11, 1919. New York, New Century [1947]. 24 p. 19 cm. (Marxist pamphlets, no. 4) 1947 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Liberator. 1918 June (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Long range program of the Zavala County program building committee [Your county program] n.d. (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Lorberg, Aileen. Otahki: Trail of Tears Princess 1967 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - La Luz: National review of La Raza.--Vol. 4, no. 2 1975 May (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Mao, Tse-tung, 1893-1976. On methods of leadership / Mao Tsê-tung. 1st ed. Peking: Foreign Languages Press, 1955. 10 p.; 18 cm. 1955 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Mao, Tse-tung, 1893-1976. Rectify the party's style in work / Mao Tsê-tung. Peking: Foreign Languages Press, 1955. 29 p.; 19 cm. "From the first edition of the Selected works of Mao Tse-tung, vol. III... Translation of Cheng tun tang ti tso feng 1955 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Mao, Tse-tung, 1893-1976. Reform our study. Peking, Foreign Languages Press, 1955. 10 p. 19 cm. "A report to a cadres' meeting in Yenan held in May 1941." 1955 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Marx, Karl. "Theses of Feuerbach" s.l., s.p. n.d. (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Mexican Americans and the administration of justice in the Southwest; summary of a report. [Washington; For sale by the Supt. of Docs., U.S. Govt. Print. Off.] 1970. 21 p. 23 cm. U.S. Commission on Civil Rights 1970 Mar. (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - The Migratory Farm Labor Problem in the United States. Washington: U.S. Government PRinting Office 1967 Mar. 15 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Mills, George, Ph. D. Lucifer and the crucifer: the enigma of the Penitentes / George Mills and Richard Grove. [Denver: Westerners c1956] 44p.: ill.; 23 cm. Reprinted from the 1955 Brand Book of the Denver Westerners for the Taylor Museum of the Colorado Springs Fine Arts Center. Bibliography: p. 41-44. 1966 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - The Mojave of the Colorado: Pages of History, Sausalito 1960 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Montana Post.--Vol. 11, no. 4 1973 Nov. -Dec. (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Monthly Review.--Vol. 4, no. 11 1953 Mar. (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Monthly Review.--Vol. 8, no. 2 1956 June (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Monthly Review.--Vol. 14, no. 10 1963 Feb. (Box 7, Folder 20)